If I have an accident, they say that its
name itself is bad. After an accident, there are
many celebrities who are
neither covered by our health insurance
nor our term insurance. The
year 2019, this time had come to a standstill. We were
not going out of our homes. People were
working from home and the
roads were running at their full capacity. That year
also, according to NCRB data,
more than three and a half lakh accidents were reported.
These are only road accidents. We will talk
about this plan which will not only
support you with food but will also take care of
your Delhi news in case of an accident.
Hello Meena, I am Manoj
Kumar. I am a Challan Insurance Advisor
and we have been improving the lives of people for the last 4 years. We have
not gone out for polishing. If you need income proof to take a claim, then you
should now be a village
goldsmith or a blacksmith, you can take a policy.
PT means Total Disability.
Whenever there is a Total Disability, then I
get a lump sum amount of money in it.
We can call Total Disability this.  It is that any two
parts of the body like today both legs or one hand or a
power grid are disabled, if these are
not recoverable then for this subscribe to us,
like,
comment,
due to this you get subscribed to the Totka channel temporarily
and
get maximum benefit, you get
subscribed to the channel till the end, in this
plan of this policy you
get Rs. 20000, the
premium is usually Rs. 10020 per year,
thank you